(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Wait, this is good.
I did it.
I infiltrated this place.
Success!
大作戦！
Great operation!
あ！みんなに見られた！
Ah! Everyone saw me!
Vestia Zeta
I can't believe you guys were watching me
this whole time! Noooo!
To be honest, I did feel eyes on me
but I knew you guys were watching. It's okay.
Anyways, it's not the time to be talking about that
because today is a special day for me! Yay!
Today is... do you know what today is?
Say it! Say it! Say it! Say it!
Yeah, today is my birthday!
Happy birthday Zeta, Happy birthday Zeta...
Selamat ulang tahun...
Happy birthday...
Gitu ga sih lagunya?
Is that how the song goes?
I don't know.
Oh, what? You're saying something? Huh?
No, skill issue?
You're saying I'm a noob as a secret agent?
Bulls... Okay, I can't say the rest. Bulls!
Your lies, you're lying! That can't be true.
I've been working hard. I've got the stamina,
and obviously the intelligence, IQ 二百。
and obviously the intelligence, IQ 200.
IQ 二百。
IQ 200.
And strength, you know, I got the power as well.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So anyways, don't you worry
because I've got the perfect thing for today.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Have you ever heard of a secret agent school?
Yeah, so back in my days... back in my days,
I've been through hell and back,
so I invited some special guests here
so we can prove that I'm the best secret agent, okay?
So, we're going to do some tests together to see
how tough it is to become a professional secret agent
like me. I'm a good example.
Anyways, it reminds me of my old 学校試験, you know?
Anyways, it reminds me of my old school exams, you know?
But to be honest, to be honest,
I don't know what we'll be doing yet, but...
Wait, oh crap! Okay,
it's almost time for the first test!
最初のテストか...
The first test...
そろそろ...
Soon...
早く行かないと！
I have to go quickly!
バイバイ！
Bye bye!
これは...？！
What is this?!
ほ、ほ、ほ？
Huh, huh, huh?
なんかさ、あれ？
It's like, what is that?
ゾンビ？
A zombie?
あれ？
Huh?
あれ？なんかさ、みこちのカマキリの威嚇ポーズにビビってる？
Wait, is he scared of Mikochi's mantis threat pose?
あ、ビビってる、ビビってる。
Ah, he's scared, he's scared.
震えてる。
He's shaking.
これみこちゃん分かりました。
Miko-chan's got it.
コイツ雑魚ゾンビです。
This guy is a weakling zombie.
雑魚。
Weakling.
ざぁ〜こ。
Noob.
コイツドMかも。ドMゾンビ。
He might be a total masochist. A masochist zombie.
叩け叩け叩け！
Hit him, hit him, hit him!
ポンコツ〜。
Piece of junk~.
ざぁ〜こ。
Noob.
ちょっと弱々ゾンビさんなんじゃない？
Isn't he just a bit of a wimpy zombie?
全然怖くないんですけど。
He's not scary at all.
弱々かも。
Maybe he is wimpy.
はぁ〜！みんな！
Haa! Everyone!
お、ゼータ！
Oh, Zeta!
遅れてごめん！
Sorry I'm late!
何、このゾンビ？
What's with this zombie?
あれは弱々ゾンビ。弱々ゾンビがいる。
That's a wimpy zombie. There's a wimpy zombie here.
エージェントスクールの最初のテストにお招きしたけど、
I invited you for the Agent School's first test, but...
ゾンビも新入生なのかな？
I wonder if the zombie is a new student too?
え、新入生？新入生なの？
Eh, a new student? Is he a new student?
そうだ。でも言葉通じないけどさ、ゾンビに。
That's right. But words won't get through to a zombie.
ゼータは言葉いろんな言葉話せるよね。
Zeta, you can speak many different languages, right?
ゾンビ語も喋れるんじゃないの？
Maybe you can speak Zombie-ese too?
言ってみて言ってみて。
Try it, try it.
OK、OK。
Okay, okay.
う、いけ。
Ugh, go for it.
ちょっと弱そうかも。
He seems a bit weak.
よし、できた。
Alright, done.
できた？
You did it?
おーい！ゾンビ！
Oi! Zombie!
何してるの！
What are you doing!
怖がらせろって言ったでしょ！
I told you to be scary, right?!
ホントに何やってたのよ！
Seriously, what have you been doing?!
怒ってる、怒ってる。
She's angry, she's angry.
ごめんあそばせ。
Apologies.
どうやら弱っちいゾンビを送っちゃったみたいね。
I probably sent over the weak zombies.
申し訳ないわね。
Sorry about that.
さて。
Anyways.
今日はみなさんにサプライズテストをご用意しました。
I called you guys here for a surprise test.
シークレットエージェントにふさわしいか確かめてみましょう。
To see if you guys are fit to be a secret agent.
なるほど。
I see.
なんかわかんないけど受ける。
I don't really get it, but I'll take it.
なんかわかんないけど受けてみるか。
I don't really get it, but let's try taking it.
受けてみよう。
Let's take it.
さてさて、みなさん落ち着いてくださいね。
Okay, okay, calm down everyone.
では、この箱の中身を当ててもらうテストになりまーす！
In this test, you will need to guess what is inside the box!
これにはあなたたちの推理力が試されます。
This requires your investigative skills.
1ラウンド目では、
For round 1,
1人30秒間だけ中身に触れられます。
you can feel the object for 30 seconds only.
楽しんでくださいね。
Have fun.
みなさんのリアクション、すっごく楽しみにしてます。
Can't wait to see your reactions.
リアクション期待してるよ、だって。
She says she's expecting reactions.
完全に理解してるから。
I completely understand.
わかってるってことね。
So you know what's in it.
じゃあ、AZKi先輩からかな？
So, maybe start with AZKi-senpai?
AZKi先輩！
AZKi-senpai!
任せてくださいよ。
Leave it to me.
頑張って。
Good luck.
これさ、みんなで協力してだよね。
We're collaborating on this, right?
情報を集めて伝えることに集中したいと思います。
I'll focus on gathering information and communicating it.
はい。
Yes.
AZKiの挑戦
AZKi's Challenge
3, 2, 1, スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
え、これ？
Eh, this?
えっと、コードのような...
Um, like a cord...
コード？
A cord?
コードのようなものではない。
It's not like a cord.
え、ちょっと待って。
Eh, wait a minute.
Frog toy
何、これ？
What is this?
え、なんかジタバタしてます。ジタバタ。
Eh, it's flapping around. Flapping.
ジタバタ？動いてる、もしや。
Flapping? Is it moving?
え、なんか動いているけど...
Eh, it's moving but...
Time's up!
なんだ、なんだ。
What is it, what is it?
フォルムが分からない。
I can't tell the shape.
変な機械なんじゃない？
Maybe it's a weird machine?
なんか足がバタバタしてるみたい。
Like its feet are flapping.
バタバタ？えー！
Flapping? Eh-!
ヤバい。大丈夫、それ？
Oh no. Is it okay?
大神ミオの挑戦
Ookami Mio's Challenge
じゃあ、ミオちゃん。スタート！
Alright, Mio-chan. Start!
怖い、怖い。何、何？
Scary, scary. What, what?
はっ、なんか。あっ。
Ha, something. Ah.
何か気づいた。
I noticed something.
でも分かったかもこれ、うち。
But I might know what this is.
え、分かった？
Eh, you know?
あー、なるほど。
Ah, I see.
はい、はい、はい。あー、元気ですね。
Yes, yes, yes. Ah, it's lively.
元気？
Lively?
完全に生きてます。
It's completely alive.
Time's up!
あー、元気だった。すご。
Ah, it was lively. Wow.
絶対生きてるんだ。
It's definitely alive.
ちょっと待って。
Wait a minute.
穏やかな表情。元気だったよね。
A calm expression. It was lively, wasn't it?
さくらみこの挑戦
Sakura Miko's Challenge
ゴッドハンド、やっていきたいと思います！
We're going to play "Got Hand"!
ゴッドハンド！
Got Hand!
3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
ひぃいいい！やだ！絶対やだ！
Hiiii! No! Definitely not!
よいしょ...！
Here goes...!
ぎゃあああ！
Gyaaaaa!
なんかに触れた模様...
It seems like I touched something...
うわあああ！
Uwaaaa!
ねえ！やめてよお！
Hey! Stop it!
ガチですか？
Are you serious?
ガチのやつ！
This is the real deal!
ねえ！やめてええ！
Hey! Stop it!
分かった？
Do you know what it is?
全然分かんない...
I have no idea...
Time's up!
終了！
全然分かんない？
You really have no idea?
終わりだよ！
It's over!
え？ゴッドハンド？
Eh? Got Hand?
ここが、ブルルルッてなって...
This part went "brrrr"...
じゃあ次はゼータ！
Okay, Zeta's next!
ゼータ行けー！
Go for it, Zeta!
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
Vestia Zeta's Challenge
行きますよ！
Here we go!
行くよ！
I'm going!
3, 2, 1, スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
うわあ！これ何？
Uwaa! What is this?
え？これ生きてるやん！
Eh? This is alive!
たぶん生きてない気がするけど...
I don't think it's alive, though...
形を確認しているのでしょうか...
Is she trying to check the shape...?
大丈夫かな？
Is she okay?
Frog toy
え？飛んでる？
Eh? Is it flying?
なんか飛びそうではあるよね。
It looks like it could fly.
飛びそう...
Looks like it...
うわあ、生きてる...
Uwaa, it's alive...
Time's up!
生きてるのかな？
Is it alive?
何なのかな？
What is it?
でもこれ、みんなで力を合わせて...
But if we all work together...
そうだね。誰か当たればいいってことだもんね。
Right. As long as someone gets it right.
THINKING TIME
なんかプロペラがついたもの？
Something with a propeller?
メカみたいなのがついてたのかな、って思ったんだけど...
I thought maybe it had some mechanical parts...
マジでみこが手を入れたときブルルルッてなったから...
Because it really went "brrrr" when I put my hand in...
アヒルのおもちゃ
Duck toy
アヒルとかの足がこう、バタバタバタってなってるのとか。
Like a duck's feet going "flap, flap, flap".
カエルのおもちゃ
Frog toy
これはズバリ、カエルのおもちゃです。
This is definitely a frog toy.
ぴょこぴょこ？
Hop, hop?
振動してたってこと？
You mean it was vibrating?
ゼータちゃん、みんなの回答まとめを。
Zeta-chan, summarize everyone's answers.
ミオ先輩の答えで！
I'll go with Mio-senpai's answer!
自信満々だったもんね。
She sounded very confident.
自信満々だったんだ、これ間違ってたらウチのド後輩なんだわ。
I was confident. If I'm wrong, I'm just a total rookie.
解答　カエルのおもちゃ
Answer: Frog toy
カエルのおもちゃかな...
A frog toy, maybe...
Good guess, that's correct!
Frog toy
あ、よくできました！
Ah, well done!
おおおお！
Oooooh!
当たってるー！
It's correct!
何がポイントだったんですか？
What gave it away?
触った感じがピタピタしてて...
It felt kind of sticky...
ペタペタ感もね。
Yeah, that sticky feeling too.
で、なんかぴょんぴょんってしてたから...
And it felt like it was hopping...
これカエルのおもちゃっぽいなって思ったんだよね。
So I thought it must be a frog toy.
じゃあ次の問題、お願いします！
Okay, next problem, please!
じゃあウチが行ってみますか。
Then I'll give it a try.
ゴッドハンド・ミオーン、行きますか。
Got Hand Mioon, here she goes.
大神ミオの挑戦
Ookami Mio's Challenge
スタート！
Start!
うわあああ！何これ！
Uwaaaaa! What is this!
頑張れ、ミオちゃん！
Hang in there, Mio-chan!
え？怖い怖い！
Eh? Scary, scary!
ミオちゃんが怖がっている！
Mio-chan is scared!
嘘でしょ？何これ？これ何なんだろう、気持ち悪い...
No way... What is this? What is it? It's gross...
何これ、何これ！怖い怖い怖い！
What is this, what is this! Scary, scary, scary!
分かった分かったじゃないの、その反応。
That reaction doesn't look like you understand at all.
Time's up!
何？いや、いやーー！
What? No, noooo!
大げさにやってるでしょ？
You're exaggerating, aren't you?
ちょっと行ってみて行ってみて、これちょっと。
You should try it too. Really.
あ、次AZKi？
Oh, AZKi's next?
AZKi先輩、頑張って。
Good luck, AZKi-senpai.
AZKiの挑戦
AZKi's Challenge
スタート！
Start!
うわあああ！やっぱそうだよね！
Uwaaaaa! I knew it!
行ってみてよ。
Give it a try.
その反応になるって。
See? That's the reaction you'll get.
もしゃもしゃしてます。
It's kind of fuzzy/shaggy.
ヒントは？
Any hints?
もしゃもしゃ...
Fuzzy/shaggy...
え、何これ？ベタベタしてる...
Eh, what is this? It's sticky...
え？何それ、きもい！
Eh? What's that? Gross!
これ多分、何かのパーツ...
This is probably a part of something...
しょて、しょて驚くよね
At first, at first you're surprised, right?
そう、最初は驚くね、これ
Yeah, you're surprised at first by this.
えええー
Eee...
でも、柔らかい、柔らかい
But it's soft, soft.
柔らかい
Soft.
優しい、優しい？
Kind? Kind?
優しい、柔らかい
Kind, soft.
これに関してはちょっとね、あの、ゼタの感覚が狂ってるかもしれない
Regarding this, Zeta's senses might be a bit off.
何、何、何、余計に怖いんだけど
What, what, what? That makes it even scarier.
え、いいのか？ここで
Eh, is it okay? Here...
いいのか？いいのか、ここで、ふん
Is it okay? Is it okay here? Hmm.
じゃ、みこ先輩頑張ってね
Well, good luck Miko-senpai.
待って待って
Wait, wait.
ゴッドハンド、出たー、出たー、ゴッドハンド
God Hand! It's out! The God Hand!
いや、これガチリアクション来るぞ
Man, a real reaction is coming.
じゃあ
Well then...
スタート！
Start!
来た、ゴッドリアクション、ゴッドリアクション出た
There it is, the God reaction, the God reaction is out.
待って待って待って、ためらっています
Wait, wait, wait, she's hesitating.
手を入れることをためらっているが
She's hesitating to put her hand in...
ためらうよね、これ一回聞いたもん
You'd hesitate, since you heard it once.
前なんか、人、人じゃないか？
Wait, earlier... isn't this a person? A person?
人、人... ゾッとするような
A person... it's chilling.
待って、何これ？
Wait, what is this?
食べ物？いやそんなことはない
Food? No, that can't be it.
まさかね
Surely not...
うわー、何か出てる、待って、何か出てる
Whoa, something's coming out! Wait, something's coming out!
ちょっとやばいことが起きてるじゃないか
Something bad is happening, isn't it?
やばいこと？
Something bad?
あの、箱の中で、事件が起きている
Um, inside the box, an incident is occurring.
マスクをしてたと思うんだよ、だからうちは、ピエロのマスクなんじゃないかと思いました
I think it was wearing a mask. So, I thought it might be a clown mask.
えっと、白い、白塗りの女性の、顔
Um, a white, white-painted woman's face.
怖えーよ！
That's scary!
マスク？マスクか
A mask? A mask, huh.
その答え怖えーよ
That answer is scary!
おそらく、YAGOOのカツラ
Probably, a YAGOO wig.
えええー！
Eeee!
絶対カツラだったと思うんだよ、あれ。ロングヘアーYAGOO
I'm sure it was a wig. A long-haired YAGOO.
ロングヘアーYAGOO？
Long-haired YAGOO?
そうだよね、可能性...
Right, the possibility...
可能性高いかも
The possibility might be high.
名探偵みこ先輩に信じようかな
I think I'll believe Great Detective Miko-senpai.
お、お
O, o
答えは！
The answer is...!
ロングヘアーYAGOO！
Long-haired YAGOO!
あちゃー、残念だね。
Uh-oh, too bad.
不正解です！
It's the wrong answer!
なんか怖いんだけど
It's kind of scary.
当たってた！当たってた！
I was right! I was right!
みこちゃん、当たってるよ
Miko-chan, it's right.
あずちゃん、当たってるよ
Azu-chan, it's right.
当たってるの怖い、怖い
Being right is scary, scary.
次の問題お願いします
Next question, please.
お願いします
Please.
じゃ、みこちゃんから行ってみますか？
Well, shall we start with Miko-chan?
名探偵、名探偵決めてね、ここで
Great Detective, Great Detective, decide it here.
名探偵、頼むよ
Great Detective, we're counting on you.
ゴーゴーゴー！
Go, go, go!
待って、待って、濡れてる
Wait, wait, it's wet.
ちょっと今日一の絶叫出たけど大丈夫？
Whoa, that was today's biggest scream, you okay?
実況してよ、実況実況
Commentate! Commentate, commentate!
なんかチクチクしてて、チクチク
It's like, prickly, prickly.
痛いってこと？
You mean it hurts?
なんか、ぬるぬるしたのが濡れてて
Like, something slimy is wet...
濡れてる？濡れてる？
Wet? Wet?
全部に、あの、トゲトゲがあります
It has, um, thorns all over it.
全部にトゲトゲが
Thorns all over it.
いっぱい、生き物？
A lot of them... are they alive?
トゲトゲした生き物、待って、いっぱいいるって何？
Prickly creatures... wait, what do you mean there's a lot of them?
え、何、何、何、今の何だった？
Eh, what, what, what? What was that just now?
どうする、あずき先輩のほうがいいかな
What should we do? Should AZKi-senpai go next?
冷静な判断できるのかな
Can she make a calm judgment?
あずき先輩、ゴー！
AZKi-senpai, go!
え、何？
Eh, what?
何か濡れてる、濡れてる
It's wet, it's wet.
やっぱ濡れてるんだ
So it is wet.
え、何か、湿って、湿っています
Eh, it's kind of... damp, it's damp.
湿っている、湿度高めなんだこれ
Damp... the humidity is high for this one.
どういうこと？
What does that mean?
え、何この、トゲトゲした球体のような
Eh, what is this... like a prickly sphere?
球体？球体と、その下にもトゲトゲしたものが
A sphere? A sphere, and there are prickly things below it too.
トゲトゲがいっぱいあるってこと？
So there are many prickly things?
痛くはないけど
It doesn't hurt, but...
痛くはない？
It doesn't hurt?
え、これ何だ？何なんだろう
Eh, what is this? I wonder what it is.
何、何、わかんない
What, what? I don't know.
めっちゃむずいんだ、じゃ
It's super hard then.
何だこれー！
What is this?!
なんか湿ってる
It's kind of damp.
みおちゃんですかね、次。最後ゼタに決めてもらう
I guess Mio-chan is next. Finally, we'll have Zeta decide.
優しい、優しい、何か嫌だなその感想聞いた状態でやる、触るのちょっと嫌だかも
Kind, kind? I don't like doing it after hearing that impression. Touching it might be a bit unpleasant.
ゴー！
Go!
嫌だな、濡れてるって前情報で嫌だ
I hate this. Knowing it's wet beforehand is the worst.
濡れてる？
Is it wet?
うわー、やっぱ濡れてるなー
Whoa, it really is wet.
濡れてる？
Wet?
おおー、濡れてる
Oh, it's wet.
けど、濡れてるけど、何か固くて、確実にたくさんいる
But, it's wet, but it's kind of hard... and there are definitely a lot of them.
たくさんいる？たくさんいるぞ、一体何なんだよ
A lot of them? There's a lot! What on earth are they?
これ、なんだ？
What is this?
え、でもこれあんまり見かけないやつの気がする
Eh, but I feel like this isn't something I see often.
見かけない？
Not something you see often?
あ、これ、おむずいんじゃない？
Oh, isn't this really hard?
むずいんだ！
It's hard!
むずいんだ。
It's hard.
出た！
I'm out!
行こう！行け！
Let's go! Go!
がんばれ、ゼータ！
Good luck, Zeta!
それでは...
And now...
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
Vestia Zeta's Challenge
スタート！
Start!
うわぁー！おおー！
Whoa! Oh!
あー、あー、おっけー、おっけー。
Ah, ah, okay, okay.
おっけー。
Okay.
お、早い。
Oh, that was fast.
おっけー。
Okay.
もしかしてこれさ、我々はあんまり馴染みないけど...
Maybe this, we aren't very familiar with, but...
ゼータは馴染みあるの？
Is Zeta familiar with it?
もしかしたら。
Maybe.
これいっぱい触ったことあるかも。
I might have touched this a lot.
ええー！馴染み深い！
Ehh! It's familiar!
馴染み深いんだよ、ゼータにとっては。
It's familiar to her, for Zeta.
なんだろう。
What could it be?
おっけー。
Okay.
我々にしたらちょっと難しいかも。
For us, it might be a bit difficult.
イエーイ！おっけー！
Yay! Okay!
ええー！
Ehhh!
これはね、うん、うん、うん...
This is, yeah, yeah, yeah...
おそらくこれは...
Probably this is...
ウニの仲間！
A relative of the sea urchin!
ウニ！？
Sea urchin!?
あずきの答えは、苔！
AZKi's answer is moss!
なんかそのちょっとずついっぱいなんか生えてる感じ。
Like, that feeling of lots of things growing little by little.
でも確かに湿ってたし、そう、湿ってたし。
But it certainly was damp, yeah, it was damp.
うちの答えは、ライチ！
My answer is lychee!
ライチ！？
Lychee!?
ゼータはね、たぶん、えっと...
Zeta, probably, um...
なんかインドネシアの果物と近いかも。
It might be close to an Indonesian fruit.
いっぱいなんかトゲトゲの...
Lots of thorns...
そう、そう、トゲトゲも。
Right, right, thorns too.
なんていう食べ物？
What's the food called?
名前は？
The name?
名前は、ランブータン、ランブータン。
The name is rambutan, rambutan.
ランブータン！？ランブータン！？
Rambutan!? Rambutan!?
でもわかんない、ここにはランブータンはいないのかな。
But I don't know, maybe there aren't rambutans here?
自信持って！
Have confidence!
そうだよ、ゼータが一番わかってた！
Right, Zeta knew the best!
一番そう、自信あったじゃん。
Right, you were the most confident.
じゃあそれでいきましょうよ。
Well then, let's go with that.
答えは、せーの、ランブータン！
The answer is, one two, Rambutan!
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding!
Correct answer!
おおー！やったー！すごい！ゼータ！
Whoa! We did it! Amazing! Zeta!
あ、ちょっと待って、うちライチとか言ったけど全然違うわ。
Ah, wait a sec, I said lychee but it's totally different.
全然違う！
Totally different!
何これ。
What is this.
ライチの味がするかも。
It might taste like lychee.
似てる。
Similar.
美味しいよこれ。
This is delicious.
初めて見た。
First time seeing it.
甘いの？
Is it sweet?
甘いかも。甘いんだ。ちょっと甘っぽい。
It might be sweet. It is sweet. A bit sweet-ish.
甘っぽい。
Sweet-ish.
新しい果物に出会いました。
I've encountered a new fruit.
There seems to have been correct and incorrect answers.
But...
Zeta!
ん？
Hm?
It seems like your investigative skills are not quite up to par yet.
You need to work harder.
Or, in other words...
Skill issue! Hahahaha!
Skill issue!?
なんていうこと！？
What!?
見て、スキルが問題のゼータだって。
Look, it's Zeta with the skill issue.
あ、怒っちゃった！
Ah, she's getting mad!
She's getting mad! Hahahaha!
Oh dear!
Wow, you can't even solve that! Hahahaha!
Everyone else, you did great!
Good luck on the next test!
See y'all!
え、ゼータも頑張ったのになー。
Eh, even though Zeta worked hard too.
ゾンビちゃん...
Zombie-chan...
さっき笑ったの？
Did you just laugh?
ちょっと舐めてた、舐めてたね。
We were underestimating him, yeah.
笑ってんじゃねーよ！
Don't you laugh at me!
笑うなよお前！
Don't laugh, you!
一生懸命やってんだぞ！
We're doing our best!
かわいそう。
Poor thing.
いじめないで。
Don't bully him.
あずき、あずき。
AZKi, AZKi.
あずちゃん優しくしてあげて。
AZ-chan, be nice to him.
もっと、床に這いつくばりなさい。
Now, grovel more on the floor.
あずき様！？あずき様！？
AZKi-sama!? AZKi-sama!?
ありがとね、みんな、来てくれて本当に。
Thank you, everyone, for coming, really.
こちらこそ！
Our pleasure!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
じゃあ、なんか、あと、今日は集めてくれてありがとね、本当に。
So, um, also, thanks for gathering everyone today, really.
次のテストの時間だから、行ってくるね！
It's time for the next test, so I'm going now!
行ってらっしゃい！頑張れ！
Have a safe trip! Good luck!
また会いましょう！
Let's meet again!
バイバイ！
Bye bye!
ゾンビ、もっと祝いなさいよ、祝いなさいよ、もっとゼータを、祝って！
Zombie, celebrate more, celebrate, celebrate Zeta more, celebrate!
Wait, there's like a ring.
Wait, is this like a boxing ring?
Wait, what am I gonna have to do here?
No way. Are we gonna have to fight? I'm not good at fighting though.
I mean, I can try. Hwah! Hwah! Hwah!
Happy birthday, Zeta!
Long time no see!
This is Amelia Watson...
hololive EN's number one time-traveling detective!
How've you been?
I've been good, how are you!?
Ah, glad to see you're doing well!
Yeah, I prepared the second test...
but we also have other transfer students.
Let's call them in now!
Don't let the first contestant's size fool you!
People tremble...
People tremble when they hear her name and her infamous line!
"Small but mighty, always rock hard, I'm rocking in!"
Please welcome... Koseki Bijou!
Koseki Bijou!
Happy birthday, Zeta!
Today I'm rock hard just for you.
Thank you! I'm honored!
KOSEKI BIJOU - TINY BODY BUT ALWAYS ROCK HARD! I'M ROCKING IN!
Coming to the ring, she's the hero we didn't ask for,
but somehow still believe in!
She's everyone's last hope,
because all the good ones were busy!
Her line is: "Meet your end, and... despair! Haiyah!"
Oh my god! Look at that walk! IRyS!
IRyS!
Happy birthday, Zeta!
I'm taking you down... down under!
IRyS - MEET YOUR END, AND DESPAIR! HAIYAAAAA!
Ladies and gentlemen, hide your dumbbells and protect your ego!
Because this grim reaper doesn't just reap souls,
she rips the gym apart!
Her favorite line is, "Only time can out-bench me."
Please welcome... Mori Calliope!
Oh my god, is that THE Mori Calliope?
Mori Calliope!
Happy birthday, Zeta!
MORI CALLIOPE - ONLY TIME CAN OUT-BENCH ME
Good!
Everyone has gathered, right?
This is probably a big surprise, huh?
And I'm sure you're all wondering what kind of test this is gonna be!
Anyone have any guesses?
Don't say ground pounding.
Oh, correct! We're holding a physical test using this long stick with these Bazo weights
to determine if you are fit enough to pass off as a secret agent!
Oh my god. Okay, that looks heavy.
Okay, okay. For level 1 of the physical test!
Strength Test Level 1: Test how many times you can lift the Bazo weights within 30 seconds!
First, lift Bazo from the ring mat up to your hips as many times as you can within 30 seconds!
For level 2, the mat will be bumpy! You'll do the same thing as many times as you can within 30 seconds.
And for the last level, you'll stand on the bumpy mat and balance a cup on your head! Make sure you don't drop it, and lift Bazo up!
Well then, are you guys ready?
Let's go!
Okay, who's ready for the physical test?
Okay, maybe we should have Bijou start first?
I got it!
She's rock hard muscles!
Okay, are you ready?
3, 2, 1, start!
One! Two!
Three! Four!
Five! Six!
Seven! Eight!
Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve!
Thirteen! Fourteen!
Fifteen! Sixteen!
Seventeen! Eighteen!
Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Time's up!
Bijou: Level 1 - 21
So IRyS, I doubt her!
I got this!
I'm gonna prove them people wrong!
Yes, my full potential!
Start!
One! Two!
Three! Four!
Five! Six!
Seven! Eight!
Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve!
Thirteen! Fourteen!
Fifteen! Sixteen!
How you doing, IRyS? Don't slow down!
Seventeen! Eighteen!
Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Time's up!
IRyS: Level 1 - 21
One more!
It's a tie, it's a tie!
Let's go! Mori's deadlifts next!
Like you said, it's more of a speed thing, isn't it?
Show us then!
Ready?
Start!
One, two, three!
Four, five, six!
Seven, eight!
Nine, ten, eleven!
Twelve, thirteen, fourteen!
Oh my god, fifteen, sixteen!
Seventeen, eighteen, nineteen!
Twenty, twenty-one, twenty-two!
Twenty-three, twenty-four, twenty-five!
Twenty-six, twenty-seven, twenty-eight, twenty-nine!
Time's up!
Oh my god... oh my god... okay, okay...
Anyway, that was me. What's the score?
Calliope Level 1: 29
29! 29!
Like I said... okay, you have to show us what you're made of.
Okay, I've got this. You guys got this. Okay, okay, okay.
You're gonna count down for me? / Of course. You ready? / Yeah!
Start!
One, two, three, four!
Five, six, seven, eight!
Nine, ten, eleven, twelve!
Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen!
Seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty!
Dang! Twenty-one, twenty-two, twenty-three, twenty-four!
Twenty-five, twenty-six, twenty-seven, twenty-eight, twenty-nine, thirty!
Time's up!
Whoa! That was awesome exercise!
I can't stand up! Help!
You did great!
Zeta Level 1: 30
But, but, but... that was painful.
She is a secret agent after all. / I feel like my soul left out of my body.
That's enough workout for this year. / Yeah.
Okay, now who's ready for Level 2?
Whoa! I don't know about this one.
Wait a minute, that's not fair. Those are... those are pebbles from hell!
Look at that, it's so nasty! / Oh my god!
That's not fair, that's not fair!
Hello. I'm loving it, they're loving it. Pebbles, you seeing this?
Oh god, I'm loving it, yeah. Oh, it hurts so... oh my god, I... okay.
Start!
One, two, three, four, five!
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen!
Sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty!
Twenty-one, twenty-two, twenty-three, twenty-four, twenty-five!
Twenty-six, twenty-seven, twenty-eight, twenty-nine, thirty, thirty-one, thirty-two, thirty-three, thirty-four!
Time's up!
Whew! Wow! Oh my god!
Was that her full power?
Bijou Level 2: 34
The rocks were helping me! They gave me strength!
Wait, IRyS is running away as we speak.
No, no, no, no! / Go on, show the world again, you have to again.
Show them who you are! You have to prove to the world that you are strong.
It's time to get massaged by the rocks. Take your time. How does it feel?
Just... just tell me when you're ready. / Ready? Start!
Start!
One, two, three, four, five!
Six, seven, eight, nine!
Ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen!
Fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen!
Eighteen, nineteen, twenty!
Wait, what's after twenty? / Time's up!
Time's up!
Yeah! You did it! You did it!
You don't have to keep standing there.
IRyS Level 2: 20
I've lost my words... I think she's... okay, 20.
I'm not gonna go that hard, I'm not that strong. / Oh, oh, oh!
Okay, the pebbles, the pebbles are gonna help me. Heh. All right.
Well, I'll try to just do my best. / You've got this! Go Mori! Double tap!
Tell me when you're ready. Ouch. All right, I'm good. / Okay, start!
Start!
One, two, three, four, five!
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve!
Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen!
Eighteen, nineteen, twenty, twenty-one, twenty-two, twenty-three, twenty-four!
Twenty-five, twenty-six, twenty-seven, twenty-eight, twenty-nine!
Thirty, thirty-one, thirty-two, thirty-three!
Time's up!
Whoa! Oh my god! Yokei, yokei! Mori, yokei!
Oh my god, I'm good. / You got more than your first time!
32! Yeah! You were focused! / I think it was 33! I counted 33!
It was... so the final count is...
32!
I'll take it.
Step on those pebbles like they want.
Who gives you permission?
Yeah, we were given permission to step on them!
(Screaming)
She's going Super Saiyan!
Something's coming out of me!
Okay, alright Zeta, are you ready?
Yeah! Three, two, one, go!
Start!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12
13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26
27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38
Time's up!
This is potential! Five, five, five! Get it!
I'm glad you guys are having fun!
Level 3 of the physical test is gonna be pretty tough, though.
You guys ready?
For level 3, I've got a little something behind me...
...which is a... A cup! A cup!
Would you like a cup of tea?
Um, maybe later. After afternoon tea time.
While you guys are stepping...
...while we are stepping on the bumpy mat...
...we're also going to be balancing this cup on top of our head like this.
You still have to use the mat.
Yeah, it's a combination of everything.
And while lifting as well, of course.
Yeah, it doesn't affect us at all! It doesn't affect us at all!
Okay, okay. Crown... crown... crown...
Crown the princess.
Oh, there you go.
It's so over. It's so over.
Are you ready people? Are you ready?
Oh, wait. Remember to use your butt and your legs.
Okay, butt and my legs.
Form is important. Form.
Yes. Oh, ready? Are you ready?
Alright. Okay, start!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9
10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20
21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28
Time's up!
How many was that?
I like how the cup was stuck on her head.
Yeah, that was funny. And then it turned over and it was hot on her head.
28! You got 28! Congrats!
IRyS, it's IRyS!
IRyS is the princess.
I have IRyS here. Beautiful posture.
Exactly. Yeah.
Show off that posture.
Okay. Yeah, this is her strong point.
Because she's very good at keeping it on her head.
Okay. Wait a second, don't put it on me yet. Don't put it on me yet.
Okay, you may place it on my head, the crown, milady.
Here goes. Thank you. Oh!
It's beautiful. My coronation. Okay.
Three, two, one, start!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9
I'm about to cry.
Time's up!
I'm proud of you.
This stupid cup! Stupid cup!
Don't blame the cup. It's not the cup's fault.
Maybe my good form will come in handy here.
Yeah, exactly. You may place the tiara on my head.
Now you have to step on it first.
Oh come on. You have to feel the pain.
It's the pain before the gain.
Yeah, you'll feel better that way. Pain before the game.
Pain is beauty. Okay. Maybe a wider stance is better.
Alright. Alright, I'll do it.
I shall place it on top of the crown, so you have double crown.
Awesome. Okay. Okay.
Are you ready coach? Maybe... maybe...
Three, two, one, start!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10!
11, 12, 13, 14, 15!
16, 17, 18, 19, 20!
21, 22, 23, 24, 25!
Time's up!
Yes! That was my goal! That was my goal!
Level 3, 24! And I didn't lose the cup even once!
You sure? Maybe there was tape.
Maybe there was tape involved.
I think she's cheating.
Is it not? Yeah, no.
Super glue? Was it super glue on IRyS's head? No!
Let's really test it. Let's really get in there and test it.
You're gonna use me as the test?
Yeah.
It's Zeta's turn.
Zeta's turn! Yeah! And you know what?
Directly right in the center of your head so that it's less likely to fall off.
This is like the best birthday ever.
Oh, yay! I'm glad.
Now then, are you ready? Three, two, one, start!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10!
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16!
17, 18, 19, 20, 21!
22, 23, 24, 25, 26!
Time's up!
Yay!
You did it! 26 is the final number.
26! Yay!
Does this mean the scores are what I think it is?
I think so!
Is anyone keeping score?
Staff-san has been keeping score for us!
Yeah! You are a winner! You are a winner! I am a winner!
Yeah! You are a winner! What are the scores again?
What matters is what's inside!
Seems like you guys completed the test! Woohoo! Some of you were able to lift pretty well.
Maybe not for some, though. It was so much fun just watching!
But come on, Zeta. You're the birthday girl!
You should be showing us your crazy skills or something! Prove it to us next test, okay?
Well then, thank you for having me! This is Amelia Watson signing off.
Until next time! Bye!
Bye Ame!
She just has really high standards, okay? Even if you won, it's not enough for her.
Well, she is a detective, so yeah. Not enough for her.
Thanks Ame! Love you! Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Good luck on your other tests!
See ya!
よし、レベル3スタート！ Darknessちゃん、あいつを狙おう！待って、Darknesss! あそこを狙おう！
Okay, level 3 start! Darkness-chan, let's aim for her! Wait, Darknesss! Let's aim at that!
あ！やめて！やめて！嫌だ！
Ah! Stop it! Stop it! No!
助けて！嫌だ！やめて！助けて！
Help me! No! Stop it! Help!
助けて！やめて！助けて！お願い！
Help me! Stop! Help! Please!
多すぎる！助けて！
It's too much! Help!
イエーイ！イエーイ！楽しそう！
Yeah! Yeah! It looks so fun!
やめて！やめて！助けて！
Stop! Stop! Help!
はいはい、楽しそう！
Yes, yes, yes! It's so fun!
楽しそう！見て見て！
It's so fun! Look, look!
ゼータ？何？これ何？なんで鉄砲持ってるの？
Zeta? What? What's this? Why are you holding guns?
やだ！やめて！やめて！嫌だ！
No! Stop! Stop! No!
撃て！撃て！やっちゃえ！
Shoot her! Shoot her! Get her!
嫌だ！やめて！助けて！
No! Stop it! Help!
あ、当たってる！見て見て！
Ah, it's hitting her! Look at her go!
待って！なんでこんなことに？やめて！
Wait! Why is this happening? Stop!
どういうこと？誰か説明して！
What does this mean? Someone explain!
Bokobokoboko~ Kobo Kanaeru at your service! Let me be your sun to shine your day! Ehe!
Zeta, happy birthday!
Thank you!
I already told them what to do before you came here, so they know the rules!
We're gonna be testing your aim skills with this water gun!
In shooting level 1, we will see how many immobile targets you can hit within 30 seconds!
In level 2, we will see how many moving targets you can hit within 30 seconds!
And level 3 will test if you can hit the targets on the moving zombie!
誰が最強のエイム力を持っているかな？
Who do you think is the best shooter here?
私！私！私！私が一番！
Me! Me! Me! I'm the best!
常闇トワたち、みんなFPSやってるんでね！
We all play FPS games, so we should be good!
そうだね。私はやってないけどね！
Yeah, right. I don't play though!
余裕余裕！余裕余裕！
Easy peasy! Easy peasy!
わー！わー！頑張ろう頑張ろう！
Whoo! Whoo! Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
負けませんよ！
I won't lose!
Level 1
こちらに！
Right here!
動かない的があるので こちらをみんなで一人ずつ打っていこうかなと思います
We have stationary targets here, so I think we'll take turns shooting them.
頑張る！はい！
I'll do my best! Okay!
順番どうしましょう？
What should the order be?
一番！一番！やりたい！やりたい！やりたい！
First! First! I want to do it! I want to do it!
まつりちゃんはいい位置で...
Matsuri-chan, at a good position...
ゼタさんにはここらへんで見てもらいましょう
Let's have Zeta-san watch from around here.
はーい
Okay.
3, 2, 1, Start!
おー！うまっ！
Oh! Skillful!
外さなし？
No misses?
まつさんがパーフェクトおじさんじゃない？
Isn't Matsu-san a perfect master?
えー？
Eh?
うますぎる！やばい！
Too good! Crazy!
残り15秒！
15 seconds left!
これみんなにはわかんないけど すっごいむずいんだからね これ
Everyone might not know, but this is really hard.
すごいすごい！
Amazing, amazing!
偏差とかもなしに...
Without any lead or compensation...
え、これ最後？
Eh, is this the last one?
お疲れ様！まつりちゃんすごい！
Good job! Matsuri-chan, amazing!
無敵に！まつりちゃんは一発も外さず 全て取れました！
Invincible! Matsuri-chan got them all without missing a single shot!
やったー！おめでとう！すごい！
Yay! Congrats! Amazing!
うますぎるよね なんかちょっと生きづらいわ
Too good, isn't it? It's a bit hard to follow that.
さぁ、私いくわ
Well, I'm going.
お、マジで？
Oh, really?
やっとトワ様でしょう 次で！りゅうじゅ...
Finally, it's Towa-sama next!
あ、トワ様だ！
Ah, it's Towa-sama!
トワ、頑張れ！いけいけ！いけいけ！
Towa, do your best! Go go! Go go!
支える、支える感じでいく？
Are you going with a supportive stance?
あ、いい、いい。じゃ、カウント...
Ah, good, good. Well, countdown...
3, 2, 1, Start!
ここ！
Here!
おー！速い速い！
Oh! Fast, fast!
ここ！
Here!
おー！速い！
Oh! Fast!
ここ！
Here!
速いぞ！最高だ！
Fast! Awesome!
ここ！
Here!
ちょっと待って、どういうこと？ うまい、めっちゃ速い！
Wait a sec, what's going on? Skillful, super fast!
ここ！
Here!
やったー！おめでとう！
Yay! Congrats!
段々越えてくんだ これ
The bar keeps getting higher.
あー、これ、これ
Ah, this, this.
次どうする？
Who's next?
いや、先にやっといたほうがいいって
Man, it's better to go earlier.
やっぱトリはね...
The finale should be...
下半身作戦 下半身作戦
Lower body strategy! Lower body strategy!
下半身を安定させる
Stabilize the lower body
下半身を安定させ ぶれないようにする
Stabilize the lower body to prevent shaking.
ポーズ ダッセぇ！
That pose is lame!
下半身作戦だど
She said lower body strategy.
ダサすぎる！
Too lame!
ポーズだっせぇ！
That pose is lame!
ダサすぎる！
Too lame!
これでいくから
I'm going with this.
3, 2, 1, どうぞ！
3, 2, 1, Go!
頑張れ！頑張れ！頑張れ！
Go for it! Go for it! Go for it!
安定して...
Stay steady...
めっちゃ回っとるやん！
You're spinning a lot!
いいよ、あれ空だぞ
That's okay, but that's the sky.
いいよあれ空だぞっ
That's the sky!
Time's up!
ラプラスの結果は、まあ、2ポイントとなります
La+'s result is, well, 2 points.
最後 いきますか？
Shall we go for the last one?
いきます！頑張れ！
I'll go! Do your best!
ということで、じゃ最後ゼタ。じゃ、撃ち殺せ！
And so, finally, Zeta. Go shoot 'em down!
1秒で、1秒で！いやいやいやいや
In 1 second! In 1 second! No no no no.
準備OK
Ready OK
準備OK 準備OK
Ready OK! Ready OK!
3, 2, 1, Go!
うわー！やったやったやった！
Whoa! I did it, I did it!
おー！いいよ！
Oh! Good job!
すごい！3個目いいよ！
Amazing! Third one is good!
おー！思ったより上手い！
Oh! Better than I thought!
上手いやん！
You're good!
うまいよー！いやーこれ、これ、これはー！
You're good! Man, this, this, this one!
全然余裕余裕。一つ目！
Totally easy, easy. First one!
うますぎる！うまい上手い！まだ、まだ、まだ！
Too good! Skillful! More, more, more!
どこ？どこどこどこ？右下、そこら辺！
Where? Where, where? Lower right, around there!
下、下、下！どこにある？
Down, down, down! Where is it?
どこだ？！
Where is it?!
あれ？どこだ？
Huh? Where is it?
なくなっちゃった...
It's gone...
いや、なんか守護霊が...
No, it's like a guardian spirit...
神様が手伝ってもらったのかも
Maybe God helped me out.
まつり先輩ナイスショット！
Matsuri-senpai, nice shot!
どこだ？！あれー？！
Where is it?! Huh?!
なんかギリギリ滑り込みで、半分取ったー！
Somehow I barely made it and got half!
やったー！クリアー！
Yay! Clear!
Level 2
あちらをご覧ください！
Please look over there!
はい。動いてる！何これ？！
Okay. They're moving! What is this?!
むちゃくちゃ。はい、頑張っていきましょう
This is crazy. Okay, let's do our best.
じゃあ誰から行く？
So, who's going first?
俺だ俺だ俺だ！私も行きたい！わー！
It's me, me, me! I want to go too! Whoa!
難しそう...
Looks hard...
もう行っちゃったから、じゃ、ラプラス様から行っちゃったからね
Since she already went, well, La+ Darknesss-sama went ahead.
いいんだ。やったもん勝ちでやばい
It's fine. It's a free-for-all, crazy.
ではいきましょう、ラプラス。いきますよ
Then let's go, La+. Here we go.
3, 2, 1, Start!
このゲームには 必勝法 がある
There is a winning strategy for this game
このゲームには必勝法がある！
There's a winning strategy for this game!
めっちゃ回っとるやん！速い速い！
You're spinning a lot! Fast, fast!
当たったー！当たったー！
I hit it! I hit it!
後ろから撃ってるのヤバいって
Shooting from behind is crazy.
当たってないよ
Not hitting
当たってないよ！当たってないよ！見て！
You're not hitting! You're not hitting! Look!
当たってないよ
Not hitting
当たってないよー！あ、速い速い！
You're not hitting! Ah, fast, fast!
うて、うて、うて、うて！
Fire, fire, fire, fire!
うて、うて、うて、うて！ぐるんぐるんだから、カメラ。
Fire, fire, fire, fire! The camera's spinning all around.
Time's up!
あとね、すごいよ1個。
Also, one of those was amazing.
あの後ろ向きでね。
You know, the one facing backwards.
絶対行きたい！絶対行きたい！
I definitely want to go! I definitely want to go!
はい、じゃあ絶対行きましょう。頑張れ、ぼたん君！
Alright then, let's definitely go. Good luck, Botan-kun!
ラプラスみたいに後ろ向かなくていい？
Don't I need to face backwards like La+?
うん、大丈夫。
Yeah, it's fine.
遊びよ…メタの調整行きましょう！
It's time to play... let's adjust the meta!
Three, Two, One, Start!
頑張れー！
Go for it!
Time's up!
あー、残念！ぼたん君、惜しいです！
Ah, too bad! You were so close, Botan-kun!
めちゃくちゃむずい…これむずいよ。
It's incredibly hard... this is tough.
いや、でも惜しかったな。
No, but that was really close.
裏がやばい、裏…裏だったからすごい惜しい。
The ones behind are the problem... that was so close since it was behind.
最後やから、まつり行かせてください。
Since it's the last one, please let me go, Matsuri.
はい、じゃあまつり先輩、行くぞ！
Alright then, Matsuri-senpai is going in!
3, 2, 1, Go!
うめ！うめ、うめ、うめ！
Nice shot! Nice, nice, nice!
マジ？あ、惜しい！
Really? Ah, so close!
Time's up!
怖いです。弱いのではありません。
It's scary. I'm not weak.
悔しい！2個か。
So frustrating! Was that two?
いや、2個もすごいよ。1だよね。
No, two is also great. It was one before, right?
なんかこれ、トワ様気づいたぞ、あっち。
I think I noticed something about that, over there.
追わない方がいい。
It's better not to chase them.
絶対そう。トワも思ってた。一点集中！
Definitely. I thought so too. Focus on one point!
アドバイスを活かして、やろうかな。
Maybe I'll try putting that advice to use.
トワチの挑戦、3, 2, 1, Go!
Towa-chi's challenge, 3, 2, 1, Go!
Time's up!
難しいんだいよ！これクソむずじゃん！
It's so hard! This is freaking difficult!
1枚でした。一緒、トワさん。一緒っす。
It was one. Same here, Towa-san. We're the same.
後ろ向いてるやつ、申し訳ないけど、後ろの人と一緒。本当にむず。
The ones facing backwards... I'm sorry, but it's the same as the people behind. Really hard.
Level 3
普通の的、動く的ときて、なんとこちら！ボーン！
First normal targets, then moving targets, and now this! Bam!
ええー！キモい！キモい！ゾンビ！
Eww! Gross! Gross! A zombie!
ゾンビの、動く的になってます。
It's a zombie, functioning as a moving target.
でも的自体は2つしかないから。
But there are only two actual targets.
確かに…こちらを狙って…なんか気持ち悪いポーズもしてます。
True... aim for these... and it's making some gross poses too.
気持ち悪い！自我がな！
Gross! It has a mind of its own!
トワチからじゃあ行きましょう。3, 2, 1, Go!
Let's start with Towa-chi. 3, 2, 1, Go!
やめてよ！イージー、イージー、イージー！
Stop it! Easy, easy, easy!
Clear
イエス！ギリギリセーフ！
Yes! Barely made it!
すごいギリギリだった。2つ獲られました。
That was a close one. You got two.
ありがとうございます。イエーイ、すごい！
Thank you. Yay, that's great!
なんかゾンビがたまに自我を持ち始めて不思議な動きをするので皆様注意を
Sometimes the zombies start to have a mind of their own and move strangely, so everyone please be careful.
行きたい、行きたい！じゃあ二ちゃんね。頑張るぞ！
I want to go, I want to go! Then it's Ni-chan's turn. Good luck!
じゃあまつりちゃん…
Then, Matsuri-chan...
まつりちゃん、3, 2, 1, どうぞ！
Matsuri-chan, 3, 2, 1, go ahead!
はやっ！はやっ！マジ？
So fast! That was quick! Seriously?
Clear
3秒で終わりました。3秒！
Finished in 3 seconds. 3 seconds!
3秒で！ええー！
In 3 seconds! What?!
さあ！
Go!
当たんないでー！怖いー！
Don't hit! It's scary!
動いてる動いてる！
It's moving! It's moving!
やばいよこれ！
This is bad!
やばいやばいこれ！
This is so bad!
今まつりちゃんが3秒で打ち抜いちゃったということは...
Since Matsuri-chan shot it down in 3 seconds...
...多分もう次ゾンビはこの動きしちゃいけないなっていうふうになって...
...the zombie will probably learn not to do that movement anymore.
やばい学習するタイプだ...
Oh no, it's the type that learns...
学習しちゃいます。
It learns.
学習ゾンビなんだ。
It's a learning zombie.
ちょっと待って、じゃあ先やる、先やる！
Wait a sec, I'll go next, I'll go next!
やっぱさ、主役が最後でしょ！
After all, the protagonist goes last, right?
3, 2, 1, ドカーン！
3, 2, 1, Bam!
Start!
あー！当たんない！
Ah! It's not hitting!
当たるんかい！
It hits me?!
なんで当たんだよー！
Why did it hit me?!
やばいやばいやばい！
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
動く動く！
It's moving! It's moving!
いいよいいよ、頭狙って！
Good, good! Aim for the head!
撃て撃て撃て！
Shoot, shoot, shoot!
あー、死なないで！
Ah, don't die!
あー当たるぞ当たるぞ！
Ah, it's gonna hit! It's gonna hit!
当たりそうだよ！
It looks like it's gonna hit!
行け行け行け！ちょっと待って待って！
Go, go, go! Wait, wait!
いいよいいよ！
Go, go!
Time's up!
やばいちょっと途中我慢できなかった...
No, I couldn't hold back halfway through...
ムカつきすぎて...
...because it was too annoying.
最後の挑戦はゼータ。3, 2, 1, ドカーン！
The last challenger is Zeta. 3, 2, 1, Bam!
Start!
うわー！
Whoa!
めっちゃ動いてるめっちゃ動いてる！
It's moving so much! It's moving so much!
行け行け行け！
Go, go, go!
私も動いてるよー！
I'm moving too!
助けてー！
Help me!
いいよいいよ、行け行け！
Okay, okay, go, go!
頑張れ！頑張れ！
Do your best! Do your best!
あと一枚！
One more!
うわー当たんない！
Whoa, it's not hitting!
やったー！すごかった！
Yay! That was amazing!
Clear
ポイントは、2倍ですねー！
The score is double!
うわーすごーい！
Whoa, amazing!
Guys! みんなー！
Guys! Everyone!
Should we see who got the most points in this fest?
めっちゃいい勝負！めっちゃいい勝負！
It's a really close match! It's a really close match!
まつりが12点、はい。
Matsuri is 12 points, yes.
でトワちんが11点、はい。
And Towa-chin is 11 points, yes.
でゼータが10点。
And Zeta is 10 points.
そしてラプラスが...
And La-plus is...
14点！
14 points!
4点！4点！
4 points! 4 points!
ラプラスが最下位ー！
La-plus is in last place!
逆から1位、逆から1位の方を選んでよ！
Hey, pick 1st place from the bottom, pick 1st place from the bottom!
Wooow! Congrats! すごーい！おめでとー！
Woooow! Congrats! Amazing! Congratulations!
You guys did very well! みんなほんとにとにかく頑張ったね！
You guys did very well! Everyone really worked hard!
And best of all, I'm glad everyone had fun. でも何より、みんな楽しんでくれて嬉しかった。
And best of all, I'm glad everyone had fun. But above all, I'm happy everyone had fun.
I can't wait to see how much more you can improve your aiming skills in the future, like me. これからもっとエイム力を上げて、こぼみたいに上手くなれるといいね。
I can't wait to see how much more you can improve your aiming skills in the future, like me.
おい。
Hey.
Um, I... I'm talking here. ちょっと……こっちが喋ってるんだけど？
Um, I... I'm talking here. Hey... I'm talking here though?
おい！こぼの話を聞いてよ！
Hey! Listen to Kobo!
Anyway, Zeta! ま、とにかくゼータ！
Anyway, Zeta!
You still have a long, long way to go...
...to become a full-fledged Secret Agent, okay?
Yeah, let's have a match one day! うん、勝負しよう！
Yeah, let's have a match one day!
Bye! See ya~ バイー！またね〜！
Bye! See ya~
(Crowd cheering)
That was such a crazy game. I got wet!
濡れちゃったよー、from the water gun.
I got wet, from the water gun.
They were shooting at me like crazy. I even had to change my clothes.
But, I heard there's going to be an announcement today.
So, are you guys ready for the announcement?
A little ad break, yes. では、告知です！お願いします！
A little ad break, yes. Now, for the announcement! Please!
じゃじゃーん！うわっまぶしい！
Ta-da! Whoa, so bright!
She's shining, she's shining so bright.
Oh my god, Zeta in an angelic outfit.
Isn't that so cute? Angel costume.
You guys have always said that you're scared of me, so you can't be scared of me now...
...cause I'm, I'm kind of, I'm the most seiso person there is.
Seiso Zeta. Seiso Zeta kita.
Seiso Zeta. Seiso Zeta is here.
どう？可愛い？可愛いんでしょ？うん、真っ白だし。
How is it? Is it cute? It's cute, right? Yeah, it's all white.
The costume looks so cute, right?
Watch out, guys, karena kapan lagi bisa lihat Seiso Zeta, ya guys...
Wait for it, guys, because when else can you see Seiso Zeta, right guys...
...berkostum, ber-cosplay sebagai angel-angel gitu.
...wearing a costume, cosplaying as an angel like that.
Lucu, iya Zeta lucu lucu. Aku mau, siapa yang mau? Aku aku!
Cute, yes Zeta is cute, cute. I want it, who wants it? Me, me!
But we don't stop here because obviously there's going to be so many more items...
...and we're going to introduce them now. じゃ、こちらをご覧ください。どうぞ。
...and we're going to introduce them now. So, please take a look at this. Go ahead!
じゃじゃーん！I'm better at counting, but that's probably six, right?
Ta-da! I'm better at counting, but that's probably six, right?
Isn't that so awesome?
誕生日記念フルセット
Birthday Commemoration Full Set
That's so cool!
So we have Acrylic Diorama...
...which you can put on your table.
Later we will explain.
And we have a cap. No cap, okay?
We have a plushie nuigurumi!
And not only that,
there will of course be voisu.
there will of course be voice packs.
Sorry, why did I say that? Voisu?
There will be voice pack.
And also bonus card as well.
Who wants bonus cards?
Me!
Birthday Set
So, I bet you guys are interested in this.
Yeah, definitely.
Kalau kalian tertarik bakal ada enam item ya guys,
If you're interested, there will be six items, guys.
acrylic diorama, haori, kucing, eh kucing,
Acrylic diorama, haori, cat... I mean cat...
ada topi, ada juga boneka,
there's a cap, and there's also a plushie.
mm... mm... mm...
いっぱいありますよね。ん、ん。
There's a lot of them. Mm-hmm.
Bonus card, there's also bonus card. So yeah.
Definitely, we're gonna get into it,
but stay, stay there. We're not done yet.
We're not done yet. We're not done yet.
はい、次どうぞ。
Okay, next please.
アンジェリックゼータ アクリルジオラマスタンド
Angelic Zeta Acrylic Diorama Stand
dajyaaaaan!
Ta-da!
This is my Acrylic Diorama. So cute.
Arutera-mama sensei, thank you so much sensei.
あ、ママありがとう！
Ah, Mama, thank you!
Mama's drawing is always so cute.
可愛いでしょうね？
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛い。
So cute.
ゼータ飛んでるよ。ほほ！
Zeta is flying. Ho-ho!
凄くない？
Isn't it amazing?
Angelic Zeta Acrylic Diorama Stand
It's super-duper cute!
I'm having an al- I almost said allergic reaction.
I am having, uh, do you know that cuteness aggression? Yeah.
That's what I'm feeling. It's so cute!
Okay!
Of course, we're gonna go to the next one.
With so much more. Mm-mm-mm.
じゃ、次どうぞ。
Well then, next please.
ベスティア・ゼータ 羽織
Vestia Zeta Haori
dajyaaaaan!
Ta-da!
何だっと？！羽織！
What's this?! A Haori!
The Vestia Zeta Haori!
I know that you guys would love to wear this
at like events, or like concerts,
or maybe you know for future fests,
next fest, I mean.
You guys can wear it together.
You can like huddle up with the same haori.
And it would be so cute, right?
I mean, I'm wearing a uniform,
so this can be your uniform.
ん、ん、ん。ライブの時とか。そう。
Mm-hmm. Like during concerts. Exactly.
可愛いでしょう？
It's cute, isn't it?
Well, mm.
If everyone like uses it together it's gonna be so cute.
If everyone uses it together, it's gonna be so cute.
lucu banget guys, haori.
It's so cute guys, haori.
Vestia Zeta Haori
Aku nggak tahu mau ngomong apa pokoknya ini keren banget,
I don't know what to say, basically this is so cool.
karena desainnya tuh pertama simpel.
Because the design is first of all simple.
Terus belakangnya tuh kelihatan Zeta.
Then the back part has Zeta on it.
Terus nggak norak gitu loh guys.
And it doesn't look tacky at all, guys.
Kayak keren aja, kayak simpel, keren, cool.
It's just cool, like simple, cool, cool.
Jadi kalian juga pakainya bisa ke mana aja nggak harus kayak konser-konser doang.
So you can also wear it anywhere, it doesn't have to be just for concerts.
You can like wear this like outside of concerts as well
You can wear this outside of concerts as well,
'cause like it's like a sophisticated,
because it's like a sophisticated...
uh, I wouldn't say elegant. It's like a cool-looking, like toned down haori, you know.
uh, I wouldn't say elegant. It's like a cool-looking, toned down haori, you know.
So befitting for me, the coolest secret agent. Okay.
Anyways, there's more.
There's more.
次の、dajyaaaaan!
Next up, ta-da!
「うええ」キャップ
"Uwee" Cap
dajyaaaaan! Wow, uwee!
Ta-da! Wow, uwee!
Uwee cap! I almost choked on myself.
It's so good! It's a baseball cap.
It's so cool! You can use this to shield yourself from the sun,
like I do because I hate the sun.
There's like 'uwee' written on top of the cap.
可愛い！「uwee」書いてあるよ。
Cute! It says 'uwee' on it.
そうそうそうそう、ゼータのセリフ「uwee」って書いてある。
Yeah yeah yeah, Zeta's catchphrase 'uwee' is written there.
可愛いでしょう？
It's cute, isn't it?
Uwee Cap
Of course there's like my neko, ah, not neko, um, my hair buns.
Of course there's like my cat... ah, not cat, um, my hair buns.
耳、耳ゼータ。
Ears, Zeta's ears.
There's my hair buns there and my, uh, ribbon.
I would call this ribbon. Ignore the whiskers, but, um,
if you can ignore the whiskers, those are not cat whiskers.
But it's cute! You can wear it. A cap!
Buy this cap! It's a good cap. No cap! Haha!
It's so cute!
Topi ya guys, apalagi panas-panas,
It's a cap guys, especially when it's hot,
harus pakai topi nggak sih guys panas-panas?
you gotta wear a cap right guys when it's hot?
Apalagi silau gitu, keren kalau pakai topi loh guys. ん。
Especially when it's glaring, it's cool if you wear a cap guys. Mm.
Terus keren lagi, hitam gitu topinya. Keren keren keren. ん。
And it's cool, the cap is black like that. Cool cool cool. Mm.
まだあるのかな？ん。ん。
Is there more? Mm. Mm.
あると思う。ん。
I think there is. Mm.
じゃ、次どうぞ。
Well then, next please.
おにえむいにゃんこ ぬいぐるみ
Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie
ううっ！いー、ううっ！
Ugh! Eeh, ugh!
It's... it's so cute!
It's a... with the cat headband, it's... it's called the Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie.
It's... with the cat headband, it's... it's called the Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie.
It looks like a cat, I know, but I swear it's not, okay?
It's not, it's um...
If you noticed, it's based on my Cat Day KV, so it's so cute, right?
みんな、あの、Cat Dayの時、覚えてる？
Everyone, um, do you remember the Cat Day time?
これ、This is the goods from last time.
This... This is the goods from last time.
Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie
It's so cute right? Look at those eyes!
It's so cute!
I want to squish it and...
...just jumble it up! It's so cute!
And she's like sleeping because, um...
I heard that cats nap for 16 hours...
...although that has nothing to do with me, I'm just saying.
Um, it's very cute, it's like sleeping.
ん〜、眠そう。眠そうゼタちゃん。
Mmm, looks sleepy. Sleepy Zeta-chan.
眠いゼタちゃん。
Sleepy Zeta-chan.
可愛い！
So cute!
Buy it or else! Or else you...
...you don't want to miss this because everyone liked the Cat Day KV.
You'll miss this.
Okay! Even more, let's see! Next please!
次！お願いします！
Next! Please!
ボイス！わぁ、ボイス！
Voice! Wha, Voice!
ボイス！
Voice!
Voice! And it's titled "A Fateful Meeting".
Last but not least, there's also a bonus...
...for who purchases the full set.
Okay, full setを...
Okay, the full set...
...買ってる人が、ボーナスをもらえるぞ。
...whoever buys it will get a bonus.
Voice Pack
Kalian dapet bonus kalau kalian beli full set, okay?
You get a bonus if you buy the full set, okay?
じゃ、Last one please!
Then, last one please!
最後！お願いします！
The last one! Please!
じゃじゃーん！Here's a bonus!
Ta-da! Here's a bonus!
うわぁ！It's the limited edition!
Whoa! It's the limited edition!
You'll get my signature! Okay!
It's so good!
Birthday Set
It's like handwritten signature and all that. Uh!
It's the best! It's limited so get it now!
Limited... スペシャルだよね。
Limited... It's special, right?
一番、もうスペシャル。んんん。
The most, most special. Mmm.
Of course, um, it's a little ad break, but we're not gonna stop there...
...because I, even though it's my birthday...
...I want to give to you things instead. Yeah!
But it's not over yet!
これで終わりじゃないよ！
This isn't the end!
It's my birthday but I also want to give you a present as well, so...
...aren't you excited?
Okay! Let's go get your present! Woo!
Are you guys ready?
Going going my way もうほっといて
Going going my way, just leave me alone
止められないね すみ任せて
I can't be stopped, just leave it to me
こりごりだ Ruleは Break it down
I'm sick of it, break down the rules
我慢できない Let me free
I can't take it anymore, let me free
目が眩んでしまいそう 鳴り響いた誓いの中で
I feel like I'm going to be dazzled by the echoing vow
憧れてただけ 然 今は何も響かない
I was just longing for it, but now nothing resonates
I know who I am am I
Brandingには興味ない 今は完全
I have no interest in branding, right now I'm completely...
無視を貫くMy greedy style
...ignoring everything, that's my greedy style
野暮ったい身も興味ない
I have no interest in unrefined appearances
ありのままでいたいの
I just want to be as I am
Going going my way もうほっといて
Going going my way, just leave me alone
止められないね すみ任せて
I can't be stopped, just leave it to me
こりごりだ Ruleは Break it down
I'm sick of it, break down the rules
我慢できない Let me free
I can't take it anymore, let me free
We are special でしょ？ 揺るがないプライド
We are special, right? My unwavering pride
それだけでいいの タラレバだらけの
That's all I need, in this life full of 'what ifs'
My life keep it Break it down Break it
We are special でしょ？ 誰に言われても
We are special, right? No matter what anyone says
私は歌うよ アンフェアばかりの
I will sing, in this world full of unfairness
この世界など Break it down Break it 進め
Break down this world, break it, and move forward
Break it down Break it 進め
Break it down, break it, and move forward
I just don't care about you
ハイテクなメイクやファッション 全然似合わないよ
High-tech makeup and fashion don't suit me at all
好みと心 誰の物でもないでしょ
My tastes and my heart don't belong to anyone else, right?
いい加減に大人だよね
It's about time I grew up, right?
Zeta-verse 誰も知らない 不完全だけど完璧な私
Zeta-verse, where nobody knows me, imperfect but perfect me
Tapi Zeta, apa adanya tidak sempurna tapi sepenuhnya diriku
But Zeta, as she is, is not perfect but she is completely me
でも、今は楽しいよ
But, it's fun right now
ありのままでいられるから
Because I can be as I am
Going going my way もうほっといて
Going going my way, just leave me alone
止められないね すみ任せて
I can't be stopped, just leave it to me
こりごりだ Ruleは Break it down
I'm sick of it, break down the rules
我慢できない Let me free
I can't take it anymore, let me free
We are special でしょ？ 揺るがないプライド
We are special, right? My unwavering pride
それだけでいいの タラレバだらけの
That's all I need, in this life full of 'what ifs'
My life keep it Break it down Break it
We are special でしょ？ 誰に言われても
We are special, right? No matter what anyone says
私は歌うよ
I will sing
...置いてばかりの世界など
...in a world that just keeps leaving things behind
Break it down
Break it to smash
Can't break me down
Breaking me...
Break it down
Let's go!
Break it to smash
Break it down
Going going my way
もう放っといて
Just leave me be
止めらんない Let me 任せて
You can't stop me, let me handle it
こりごりだ Ruleは Break it down
I'm sick of rules, break it down
我慢できない Let me free
I can't take it anymore, let me free
Thank you, everyone!
That was "Break It Down"!
Ze_cretary, if you liked it, make some noise!
MISSION COMPLETE!
MY WORLD WOULD NOT BE COMPLETE WITHOUT U, ZE_CRETARY!
YOUR SUPPORT MEANS THE WORLD TO ME! :D
LET'S KEEP DOING MISSIONS TOGETHER, FOREVER.
KEEP BREAKIN' IT DOWN!